<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ella Devenny&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://elladevenny.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ella Devenny&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://elladevenny.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 1995 Nebraska Huskers vs. the 2019 LSU Tigers</title>
      <link>http://elladevenny.github.io/2021/04/18/the-1995-nebraska-huskers-vs-the-2019-lsu-tigers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elladevenny.github.io/2021/04/18/the-1995-nebraska-huskers-vs-the-2019-lsu-tigers/</guid>
      <description>Some claim the 1995 Huskers are the best team in college football history. After the LSU Tigers won the 2019 national championship, many compared them to the infamous Huskers team, and some even claim that they are now the best team in college history.
I was intrigued by this, given that the teams were in two different decades I wanted to dive deeper into the stats and come to the bottom of this discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does the SEC really produce the most NFL players?</title>
      <link>http://elladevenny.github.io/2021/04/04/does-the-sec-really-produce-the-most-nfl-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elladevenny.github.io/2021/04/04/does-the-sec-really-produce-the-most-nfl-players/</guid>
      <description>A lot of college football fans, particularly those that support a team in the SEC conference, claim that the SEC is the best conference in college football. The SEC conference is packed with a lot of talent and are always strongly represented in rankings like the AP Top 25 Poll.
If we dive into data focused on NFL players from the 2020-2021 season, is the SEC really dominant when it comes to NFL player production?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Ella Devenny</title>
      <link>http://elladevenny.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elladevenny.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Ella Devenny and I am currently a student at the University of Nebraska- Lincoln. I am majoring in sports media and communication, with a minor in Law and Business. I have taken several courses that have expanded my knowledge with R-studio, and I am excited to be creating my first blog. I am creating projects currently for my &amp;ldquo;Sports Data Visualization and Analysis&amp;rdquo; course, in which I will be uploading to my blog!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
